(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-29T21:55:41.892781",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
んーーー！
Nnn—!
みんないる〜？(・0・)
Everyone, are you here~? (・0・)
なのなのら！
Na no na no ra!
絶対忠誠♡なのなのなら！
Absolute loyalty♡ if that's the way it is!
お菓子の国のお姫様
Princess of the Kingdom of Sweets,
とびきりプリティな0歳児
A super pretty 0-year-old!
ピアノだって弾けるんだし
I can even play the piano,
赤ちゃんじゃないのらよ！
I'm not a baby!
ワガママだって言うけれど
You might call me selfish,
ルーナはお姫様なのだから
But since Luna is a princess,
ルーナイト達も執事も
All the Lunaites and butlers,
いちいちうるさいのら！
Are always so noisy!
さあ、ルーナイト達！
Now, Lunaites!
準備はできたのら？ 出陣なのら！
Are you ready? Time to march!
パフェもシュワシュワも早く用意するのら！
Hurry up and get the parfaits and sodas ready!
あれもこれも食べたいのら！
I want to eat this and that too!
美味しいのはひとりじめ
Hogging all the delicious treats to myself,
まずいのや苦いのはルーナイト達に差し入れ！
And giving the bad or bitter ones to the Lunaites!
チョコレートの噴水も
A chocolate fountain,
キャンディの首飾りも
And a candy necklace too—
素敵なのたくさんあるのら！
There are so many wonderful things!
だからルーナのために集めてきてね！
So gather them all up for Luna!
絶対絶対絶対約束なのなのら！
Absolute, absolute, absolute promise!
まわるまわるまわるルーナ
Spin, spin, spinning, Luna!
まわるまわるまわるルーナっとのら
Spin, spin, spinning, Luna-n-nora!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回ってもっとぐるぐる回って
Spin round and round, spin even more round and round!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回ってみんなくるくる回って
Spin round and round, everyone spinning round and round!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる空いてもっとぐるぐる回って
Spin round and round in the sky, spin even more round and round!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる笑ってずっとぐるぐるまわるーな
Smile round and round, and keep spinning round and round, Luna!
ぐるぐる地球は回り始め幾億年
The Earth has been spinning round and round for hundreds of millions of years since it began,
いつまでもこのまま回るみんなに幸せを…
Bringing happiness to everyone spinning on like this forever...
まわり続くまわるのだ
Continuing to spin on and on,
ますますます社会がぐるぐるま…あれ？
Society spins more and more... Huh?
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回ってもっとぐるぐる回って
Spin round and round, spin even more round and round!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回ってみんなくるくる回って
Spin round and round, everyone spinning round and round!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる笑ってもっとぐるぐる笑って
Laugh round and round, and laugh even more round and round!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる踊ってみんなくるくる踊って
Dance round and round, everyone dancing round and round!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回ってもっとぐるぐる
Spin round and round, spin even more round and round!
んな〜
Nnā~
ぐるぐるまわる まわるルーナ
Spinning round and round, spinning Luna
まんなかちぇん…
Right in the center...
いつもおとぎ話のお姫様
Always in fairytale style, Her Highness,
はい！
Yes!
みんなの輝くお月様
Everyone's shining moon and stars!
今日は おやすみして Good night!
Today is a day off, night-night!
重い王冠は 置いておいて
Leave heavy crowns behind!
どっちの私も好きになってくれますか？
Which ever me it is, won't you love me?
どっちも欲しいから まんなかにいたくなるの
Whichever I want, I want to be right in the center!
スニーカーとシャツに着替えて
Changing into sneakers and a shirt,
歩き出したんだ
I stepped out!
出発のアラームは
The departure alarm is...
新しい私
A brand new me!
両腕をいっぱいにしても
Even if I open my arms wide,
ぎゅっとしたい この気持ち
This tight-squeezed feeling...
入らない はち切れて なっちゃう!
Can't fit inside, it bursts!
迷ってるなら まんなかなんだよ
If you're hesitating,
まんかいの青春 満腹に摂取
Full of youth, full of intake,
満天流星群 満月に heaven
Full of shooting stars, full of heaven,
満面の笑顔にして 満点すぎる思い出
Full of smiles, full of perfection!
ママるな Happy day!
Mama Luna Happy day!
ど真ん中でプリンセスを
Make the center princess,
忘れるくらいに
So much you'd forget,
胸まんたんにきゅってしてみたい
Heart pounding to the fullest!
どっちだってホントの私
Whichever it is, the real me
ままたきしたら 君のど真ん中
In the blink of an eye, right in the center!
まんなかに重なるちぇん
Right in the center, overlapping points,
まんなかでよくばるちぇん
Right in the center, greedily wanting points,
まんなかのまんなかちぇん
Right in the center, the center point,
恋する女の子のいいとこ取りで
Taking the best parts of a falling-in-love girl,
照れ隠しと素直の今 まんなかちぇん
Shy hiding and honest right in the center!
ひざまずきなさい。
Kneel down!
次はこの城の扉を叩いた者よ。
The castle door has been knocked down!
誓いなさい。
Pledge your loyalty!
このルーナの盾となり矛となり
Becoming Luna's shield and sword,
夜はぐっすり眠れるまで
Until you can sleep soundly at night,
共にあること！
To always be together!
捧げなさい！姫命（めい）で命ず！
Dedicate yourselves! Princess, order!
守ってルーナイト
Protect, Ru-Knight!
止まるな！ルーナって？
Stop, Luna!
紅茶のカップがちゃがちゃ鳴らさないってえらい！
Not rattling the teacup, brilliant!
スコーンだってこぼさず綺麗に食べてすごい！
Not spilling the scone, eating so cleanly, amazing!
たまに王冠どっちが前か間違っちゃうのかわいい！通ってよし！なのだ！
Sometimes crown, which is front? Making a mistake is cute! Pass, right? That's right!
開城〜！
Castle gates, open wide!
ルーナイト 第一条！
Ru-Knight, Article 1!
誰よりルーナが好きな人！
Whoever loves Luna the most!
ルーナイト 第二条！
Ru-Knight, Article 2!
白くのお布団持ってきて！
Bring fluffy futons!
ルーナイト 第三条！
Ru-Knight, Article 3!
3時のお茶会遅れる人守れなかったら即刑罰！
Anyone who sleeps through 3 PM tea party gets executed instantly!
分かってほしいのなら…
If you want me to understand...
これも帝王学を学ぶため…
This too is to learn imperial studies,
愛という名の教育なのら〜！
An education named love!
守ってルーナイト 想ってくれないと
Protect, Ru-Knight! Thinking of me,
プロムナード ボイコット なののなのら！
Promenade and boycott! That's how it is!
手の甲に忠誠 誓いのChu！
Pledge loyalty on the back of your hand, Ch-U!
ガラスの靴 履かせてワルツ！
Let me wear glass slippers and waltz!
守ってルーナイト かまってくれないと
Protect, Ru-Knight! If you don't pamper me,
ブラウニーにキャンディー どれだけあってもね
Brownie and candy, no matter how much you give me,
君がいないきゃだって！みんな
Because I need you, everyone!
心して捧げなさい！
Make it heartfelt and dedicate yourselves!
姫で命ず！
Princess's order!
守ってルーナイト 想ってくれないと
Protect, Ru-Knight! Thinking of me,
プロムナード ボイコット なののなのら！
Promenade and boycott! That's how it is!
永遠の忠誠 この指にChu！
Eternal loyalty on this finger, Ch-U!
ガラスの靴 履かせてワルツ！
Let me wear glass slippers and waltz!
守ってルーナイト かまってくれないと
Protect, Ru-Knight! If you don't pamper me,
ブラウニーにキャンディー どれだけあってもね
Brownie and candy, no matter how much you give me,
君がいないきゃだって！みんな
Because I need you, everyone!
心して捧げなさい！
Make it heartfelt and dedicate yourselves!
姫で命ず！
Princess's order!
んない！みんなおにょー！
Nnā~ everyone! Hello!
おのらぶ4期生 姫森ルーナナナナ〜！
This is Himemori Luna's...
今日はぶのたんのサンタさんライブ！イェーイ！
Today is the Bruno-tan Santa-san Live! Yay!
みんな来てくれてありがとーー！
Thank you everyone for coming!
今日のハッシュタグはこちら！これでいっぱいツイートしてください！
Today's hashtag is right here! Please tweet lots!
おお おおきょくめだね どうだった？
Oh, this is the third song. How was it?
かわいかった？ ふむふむ… 分かってたのら。
Was it cute? Hmm hmm... I knew it was cute!
そして 今日のステージも見てください！
And please check out today's stage too!
すげえ！雲だらけ！
Amazing, so many clouds!
あっちのさ、この雲の向こう、何があるのだろうかな？
Over there... I wonder what's beyond these clouds?
みんなも予想してみてね。
Everyone try guessing too!
そして 今日のライブテーマはルーナリバースデイです！
And today's live theme is "Luna Reverse Day"!
どんな意味があるのかはてさて、そして、守ってルーナイト！
What does that mean, well... And protecting Lunaights!
歌ってる時にね、ルーナイト大大変身しました。みんな気づいてくれたのかな？
When I was singing, Lunaights underwent a huge transformation. Did you notice?
100万人記念で新モデルになりました！
To commemorate 1 million subscribers, we got a new model!
そしてポルナイトがなんかルーナイトに魔法をかけてくれたのらね。
And Polnight cast some magic on Lunaights, right?
あ、ポルナイト！おや！ひめ、ひめ、ほい！ひめ、どこにいるのら？
Ah, Polnight! Hoy! Princess, where are you?
わあ、この雲の向こうにいます！
Wah, they're beyond these clouds!
そうなのだな！ねえねえ、私の姿、どう、どう、どう？
That's right! Hey, how's my appearance?
せっかくだから姫の以前の姿を出して比較してみよう！
Let's bring out my previous appearance and compare!
あ、いいね！あ、光って出て、出たパネルが出そう！出た出た出た！
Ah, nice! The panel is coming out! It's out!
ではではまずは足元から見ていきましょう！
Well, first let's look from the feet!
あ、そうそうそう。あ、ポルさん、いい感じですよ、のらね、これ。
Ah, yeah. Pol-san, this feels pretty good, right?
なんかこれ影の感じとか変わった？おっと？
Somehow, did the shadow feel change? Oh?
スカートとかポスターでの感じ変わったね！かわいい！いい感じ！
The skirt and posture feel different! So cute!
あ、待って、ここらへんとかも待って、あっ、筋トレの効果？
Wait, around here too... Ah, muscle training effect?
え？で、でてるじゃん！なになに？でてるでてる？
Eh? It's showing! What's this? Is it showing?
最近筋トレしてる？やってるよ、パーソナルだけどな。
You been muscle training? I do it, though it's personal!
あ、そうそうそう。後ろ向いて、後ろ後ろ！え、後ろ？お、おおいよ。
Ah, right. Turn around, back view! Eh, back? O-oh.
わあ！え、これこれ！ねえ、見てこれ！髪の毛の幽霊、あとシルエットとか！
Whoa! Look at this! Hair silhouette and everything!
これめっちゃいいじゃん！おっと、後ろ姿やばい！
This is so good! The back view is amazing!
そしてね、ルーナイトの手も見てほしいのだな！
And you should also see Lunaight's hands!
まあ、お手てがまあ、小さくてかわいいね！いいでしょ？
Well, the hands are so small and cute! Right?
手相も！あ、手相ね？うん。
Palm lines too! Ah, palm lines? Yeah.
あとお顔も見て、お顔このパネルと比べられるのちょっと難しいんだけど、
And look at the face too, comparing it to the panel is hard, but
斜めから見た時にの、あ、フェイスラインとか変わったね！かわいいじゃん！
When viewed from an angle, the face line changed! So cute!
パパ、ありがとう！
Papa, thank you!
うん、ぜひみんなもね、過去の3D配信と見比べてほしいのだな！
Everyone please compare it with past 3D streams!
ねえねえ、ポル、ポルナイトさ、質問があるんだけど、そっちの雲の向こうってどうなってるのだな？
Pol-night, I have a question, what's beyond those clouds?
武道館の会場あるよ！来る？え？マジ？入れよ！うん、バッシャー！
There's the Budokan venue! You coming? Really? Put me in! Yeah, splash!
え、ばっ、ばっ、バッシャー！？うわあ、めっちゃ光ってる！
Eh, spl-splash?! Whoa, it's glowing so much!
でけえ！これームーンギャラクシーの時ステージにくっついてた馬車なのだよ！
Huge! This is the carriage from the Moon Galaxy stage!
というわけで姫、乗ってください！乗れるの？乗ってください！
So princess, please get in! Can I ride? Please!
乗るのだな！
I'm riding!
うわあ、すごい！中も豪華なのだな！
Whoa, amazing! The inside is luxurious too!
ちょっとここ座ってみるのだな。よっしょ。
Let's try sitting here. Yoisho.
ルーナイトの人形もあるのだね！すごい！
There are Lunaight dolls too! Amazing!
準備はオッケーですか？
Are you ready?
まちだ！出発進行なのだ！
Wait! Departure, go!
よし、飛びますよ！
Alright, we're taking off!
え、待った！動いた！うわあ、進むのだ！
Eh, wait! It moved! Whoa, it's moving!
すげえ！この馬車飛んでるのだな！
Amazing! This carriage is flying!
よし、よっしょ、よっしょ、こっち見てみよう。
Alright, yoisho, let's look over here.
うわあ！すごお！
Whoa! Amaaazing!
星と雲がめちゃくちゃ綺麗なのだな！
The stars and clouds are so pretty!
うわ、眺め最高なのだね！
Whoa, the view is the best!
ごたごた、ごたごた増すわ。
Rolling, rolling more.
いいのだな！こっちからも見てみるのだな！
This is great! Let's look from this side too!
こっちもすごい！眺め最高！
This side is amazing too! The view is the best!
うわあ、いい感じなのだな！高いなあでもここ。
Whoa, it feels great! But it's high here.
大丈夫なら進んで、向こうが生見えなのだよ！
Will we be okay going forward? You can see right through!
このポルニカイドにお任せあれ！
Leave this carriage ride to me!
しっかり掴まっててください！
Hold on tight, okay?
え、大丈夫？本当とに？
Are you okay? Really?
本当に大丈夫？
Really okay?
やばいんじゃないの？雲来てるよ！
Wait, is that a cloud?
わ、わ！もう来てる！うわあああ！
Whoa, whoa! It's hitting us! Ahh!
あたし今最上級に可愛いの
Right now, I'm at my absolute cutest!
君に振られて最上級に可愛いの これが乙女の逆襲だ！
Ever since you dumped me, I've been at my cutest, because this is a maiden's counterattack!
もう気づいてるかも しれないけど言うわ
You might have already noticed, but I'll say it anyway—
あたしね 今とても 可愛い！
I am, even now, so very cute!
君が始めた恋 君が終わらすなんて なんだそれ 泣いちゃうぞ
The love you started, you're just going to end it like this? What is that supposed to mean, I'm gonna cry!
可愛い！
Cute!
あたしの連絡だけ通知OFFにしてたなんて 友達から聞いたよ
I heard from a friend that you had my contact info blocked or something!
連絡しすぎだって君が不安にさせるからじゃん もう気にしてないけどだって今
Saying you texted too much because it made you uneasy—well, I don't care anymore, but still!
君に振られて最上級に可愛いの 自分史上1番ときめき放つわ
Dumped by you, I've become the cutest ever, releasing the most heart-fluttering vibe in my life!
最上級に可愛いの 認めなよこれが乙女の逆襲だ！
At my absolute cutest, admit it, this is a maiden's counterattack!
さすがに失恋直後は 涙でぐちゃぐちゃで 可愛い！
Naturally, right after a breakup, I was a mess of tears, but cute!
君が泣かせたのに 雑なサヨナラだった なんだそれ 泣いちゃうぞ
Even though you were the one who made me cry, it was supposed to be a casual goodbye—what is that, I'm gonna cry!
可愛い！
Cute!
二人しか知らないって言ってた話だって どうしてあのこも知ってるの
You said it was a secret only the two of us knew, so why does *she* know about it too?
別れてよかったなんて思わせないで欲しかった
I didn't want you to make me feel like I was glad we broke up!
好きだったから…
Because I loved you...
君に振られて最上級に可愛くなりました もしれありがとう最上級に可愛くなれたってね
Dumped by you, I became the cutest ever—actually, thank you so much for letting me become this cute!
言って知って あいつがなんか可愛くなったってねえ聞いて
Hey, listen, they say I've gotten kind of cute—hey, listen!
君に振られて最上級に可愛いの 自分史上1番ときめき放つわ 最上級に可愛いの 認めなよこれが乙女の逆襲だ！
Dumped by you, I'm at my absolute cutest, releasing the most heart-fluttering vibe in my life! Admit it, this is a maiden's counterattack!
最上級に可愛いの
At my absolute cutest!
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a devoted Cinderella!
退屈な月曜日 あなたの香りで目覚めるの 纏ったトップノート そうよ秘密の物語なの
A tedious Monday, waking up to your scent—a lingering top note, yes, our secret story.
うまくリプレイできない 震えるハート 焦り 恥じらい 空回り…
A trembling heart that can't be replayed smoothly, impatient, embarrassing clumsiness...
誘うファンタジー 重なっちゃうくらい 一途だもん あなたに夢中です♡
A tempting fantasy, so overlapping it's like pure devotion—I'm crazy about you!
Ah バズっちゃバズっちゃやだね かまってかまってもっと 誰もがあなたを狙っちゃう
Ah, it went viral, no way! Hey, give me more attention! Everyone's gonna target you, you know?
ウインクひとつでメロメロにしちゃって こっちの知らないで
Melt them away with just a wink, without even caring how I feel!
もー！バズっちゃバズっちゃやだ ねぇ射抜いて射抜いてずっと！
More! It went viral, no way! Hey, shoot right through me!
いつでもあなたに翻弄ちゅう 誰よりあなたのトクベツでいたいの
I'm always under your spell, wanting to be your special one more than anyone else!
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a devoted Cinderella!
どんな道が待ってても
No matter what path awaits me,
ガラスのヒールで駆けくよ
I'll run through it in glass heels.
魔法が解けても覚めない夢を
A dream that won't fade even if magic wears off,
あなたにあげる
I'll give it to you.
だからぜったい負けない！
So I'll never give up!
脈打つビート
A pulsing beat,
純愛したい！真っ直ぐに
I want to love purely! Straightforwardly,
想うエンパシー 伝わっちゃうくらい
An empathy of feelings, enough to get across,
本気だもん
Because I'm dead serious!
まさしく 無敵です♡
Truly invincible♡
Ah ハマってハマっていいよね ディグってディグってきゅんと！
Ah, it's okay to fall for me! Dig and dig, with a thump!
恋する乙女は変幻自在
A maiden in love is versatile.
「キレイ」も「キューティー」も欲張りに励めば
If you greedily strive for both 'pretty' and 'cute',
輝く自分になるの
You become a shining version of yourself.
さあ！ハマってハマっていいよね 気づいて気づいてちゃんと！
Come on! It's okay to fall for me! Notice properly!
まだまだ乙女は日進月歩
A maiden's progress is still day-by-day.
世界で一番のドキドキがほしいの
I want the most heart-pounding thrill in the world.
あなたいけない プリンスですっ
You naughty prince♡
Ah 「好き」って「好き」ってなんで そうズキってズキっていうの？
Ah, why do people say 'I like you'? Why do they say 'thump'?
けなげなココロは困惑中
My devoted heart is in turmoil.
愛しさふくらんで こんなにも苦しいの
My affection swells up, and it hurts so much.
いますぐこっちに微笑って！
Smile at me right now!
Ah バズっぢゃバズっぢゃやだね かまってかまってもっと！
Ah, don't let it go viral without me! Pay attention to me more!
誰もがあなたを狙っちゃう
Everyone's gonna target you.
ウインクひとつでメロメロにさせちゃって
Make them completely infatuated with just a wink,
こっちの気も知らないで！
Without even caring how I feel!
もー！バズっぢゃバズっぢゃやだね ねぇ射抜いて射抜いてずっと！
Geez! Don't let it go viral without me! Hey, pierce through my heart forever!
いつでもあなたに翻弄ちゅう
Always being toyed with by you.
誰よりあなたのトクベツでいたいの
I want to be your special someone more than anyone else.
あぁ なんでぜたかな…？ 許してね♡
Ah, why am I like this...? Forgive me♡
あたし ひたむき シンデレラ！
I'm a devoted Cinderella!
スキスキスー フワフワフー
Suki-suki-suuu, fuwa-fuwa-fuu
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
This feeling is a melting melody
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but it's not a dream.
お願いね マイメロディ
Please, My Melody.
オトナじゃない オトメです。
I'm not an adult, I'm a maiden.
恋するのが仕事です
My job is to fall in love.
君の名前つぶやくと ドキドキするの
When I murmur your name, my heart beats fast.
聞き分けない この胸が 歌い出して止まらない
This unruly heart of mine starts singing and won't stop.
上手じゃなくてゴメンナサイ
Sorry I'm not good at this,
だけど聞いて とどけ マイメロディ
But please listen, reach them, My Melody.
マイメロディ マイメロディ
My Melody, My Melody
星空を越えて 君の夢 守るリボン
Crossing the starry sky, a ribbon protecting your dreams.
マイメロディ ハート見つけたら グルグル巻きしちゃうからね
My Melody, if I find a heart, I'll wrap you up in it!
wow wowwo 覚悟しといて 嘘じゃない
Wow wowwo, be prepared, it's no lie.
オトナじゃない オトメです。 泣いたりだってしちゃいます
I'm not an adult, I'm a maiden. I might even cry.
女の子って魔法で作られたの
Girls are made of magic.
スキスキスー フワフワフー
Suki-suki-suuu, fuwa-fuwa-fuu
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
This feeling is a melting melody
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but it's not a dream.
お願いね マイメロディ
Please, My Melody.
キライじゃないってゆーかスキ
Not that I hate you, I like you.
スナオになんてなれません
I just can't be honest.
君の笑顔見るだけで フニャフニャするの
Just seeing your smile makes me go all mushy.
それなのにー それなのに！ 憎まれ口 撃ちまくり
Even so, even so! I keep firing snarky remarks.
ひとりになって落ち込んで 枕パンチ！！
Then I end up alone and depressed, punching my pillow!!
だからマイメロディ マイメロディ マイメロディ
So, My Melody, My Melody, My Melody
本当の気持ち 風になって結ぶリボン
My true feelings turn into the wind and tie a ribbon.
マイメロディ マイメロディ 歌えオトメゴコロ
My Melody, My Melody, sing, maiden heart!
来る来る恋 つかまえちゃえ
Catch the coming, coming love!
WOW WOW WO 逃がさないから
WOW WOW WO, 'cause I won't let you escape!
ここへ来て
Come here!
キライじゃない ツライです(T-T)
It's not that I hate it, it's just painful (T-T)
真っ赤になってなっちゃいます
I'm turning all bright red!
女の子って不思議で作られたの
Girls are made of mysterious things...
とどけ
Reach out,
マイメロディ マイメロディ マイメロディ
My Melody, My Melody, My Melody!
星空を越えて キミの夢 守るリボン
Crossing the starry sky, the ribbon protecting your dreams!
マイメロディ ハート見つけたらな
My Melody, if I find your heart,
グルグル巻きにしちゃうからね
I'll wrap you up round and round!
WOW WOW WO 覚悟しといて
WOW WOW WO, so be prepared!
嘘じゃない
It's no lie!
オトナじゃない オトメです。
I'm not an adult, I'm a maiden.
泣いたりだってしちゃいます
I might even end up crying.
女の子って魔法で作られたの
Girls are made of magic...
スキスキスー フワフワフー こんな気持ち メロメロディ
Ski-ski-su, fuwa-fuwa-fu, this feeling is melo-melody!
夢だけど 夢じゃない お願いね マイメロディ
It's a dream, but not a dream, please, My Melody!
マイメロディ マイメロディ
My Melody, My Melody!
聴き惚れてるな？
Are you enchanted?
あと、オトメロディ 3曲連続で歌いましたー！
Also, I sang three Otomelody songs in a row!
えー、くぼが晴れたステージってこうなってるのなんだね！
Eh, so this is what a stage with clear clouds looks like!
次でっけえ 雲みたいなのなんだね！
Next, that huge cloud-like thing!
あ、ここ見て！シャンデリアがあるのなんだね！
Oh, look here! There's a chandelier!
じゃ、普通階段すするって場所なんだね！
And this is the place to walk up normal stairs!
あと、後ろの上の方ってこうなってたんだー！
Also, the upper back area looks like this!
見て！すごいかわいい！
Look! It's so cute!
あらの、これ天窓じゃん！どうかなるんだね！
Oh my, this is a skylight! It changes like this!
すごい、あ、待って、ルナリバースデイの看板もあるのなんだね！
Amazing, oh wait, there's even a Luna RebirthDay sign!
今日はルナリバースデイだからね！見て見て、すごいかわいい！
Today is Luna RebirthDay, after all! Look, look, it's so cute!
ん？なんだ？なんだ？なんだ？
Hm? What's this, what's this?
最高だったよ！
That was amazing!
え？誰だ誰？ポルナイトじゃないか！
Eh? Who's that? It's Polnight!
ねぇ、実はね、姫にはまだ隠された姿が残されているのって！
Hey, actually, the princess still has a hidden form left!
え、なになになになのな？
Eh, what what what is it?
ポルナイトの魔法でそのお姿にして見せましょう！
I'll show you that form using Polnight magic!
え、ほんとに？なになに、どきどきどきどき！
Eh, really? What, my heart is pounding!
ででーん！わあ、すごいかわいい！
Tada! Wow, super cute!
新しいヘアスタイルなんだね！
It's a brand new hairstyle!
ポルナイトがプレゼントしてくれたのなんだね！
Polnight gave it to us as a present!
よし、じゃあ、この新しい髪型で歌っちゃうのな！
Alright, then let's sing with this new hairstyle!
あなたのアイドル サインはB ♡ (Chu)
Your idol, signature is B ♪ (Chu)
(B小町！フーフー！)
(B-Komachi! Fuhu!)
ようやく会えたね 嬉しいね
We finally got to meet, I'm so happy.
待ち遠しくて 足をバタバタしながら
While waiting impatiently, kicking my feet,
今日楽しみで 眠れなかったよ
I couldn't sleep because I was so excited for today!
緊張なんかしてる場合じゃない イクン
This is no time to be nervous, let's go!
1分1秒 無駄になんてできないさ
Not a single minute or second can be wasted!
さあ 始めましょう
Now, let's begin!
君も！君も！君も！
You too! You too! You too!
お待たせいたしました 手を鳴らせ いらっしゃいませ
Thanks for waiting! Put your hands together, welcome!
「好き」が集まる場所へようこそ
Welcome to the place where "likes" gather!
日常はクロークの中
Everyday life is left in the cloakroom.
ここに来たなら 踊らにゃ損 損 損
If you came here, it'd be a loss not to dance!
人が居ようが居まいが 関係ない
Whether people are here or not, it doesn't matter!
箱が大き小さいとか 気にしない
Whether the venue is big or small, don't worry about it!
ちゃんと見えてる 君のサイリウム
I can see your glow sticks clearly!
今はフーっと吹けば飛ぶような 小さな小さな才能だけど
Right now, it's just a tiny, tiny talent that blows away like puff,
私を推してくれるのなら バクレスを上げる
But if you're going to support me, I'll give you a huge response!
爆レスをあげる
Giving you my explosive fanservice!
あなたのアイドル
Your idol,
サインはB♡ チュッ♡
The sign is B♡ (Chu♡)
あいつは俺が育てたって
"I raised that person,"
近い将来自慢してほしいよ
I want you to brag about it in the near future!
こうしちゃいられない
We can't just stay like this!
君と 君と 今を 楽しまなきゃ
We've gotta enjoy right now with you, and you!
引きこもりも人見知りも
Even shut-ins and shy people,
普段と違う顔見せてよ
show me a different face than usual!
みんな兄弟 調子どうだい
Hey brothers, how's it going?
なりふり構わずに そう！そう！そう！
Without caring about appearances, yeah!
他人には笑われていても関係ない
It doesn't matter if others are laughing at you!
周りがどうとかこうとか気にしない
Don't care about what those around you say!
主張強すぎ 君のサイリウム
Your penlight is way too assertive!
たとえ世界が私を拒んで
Even if the world rejects me,
ひとりぼっちを感じたとしても
and I feel all alone,
アナタが味方でいてくれたら
as long as you are on my side,
怖いものはないよ
I have nothing to be afraid of!
見てよ 見てよ 何が始まる
Look, look, what's about to begin?
君との物語が
Our story—
鳴呼 なんて素晴らしい景色だ！
Oh, what a wonderful scenery!
客席が居ようが居まいが関係ない
It doesn't matter if there's an audience or not!
会場が大きい小さいとか気にしない
Don't care if the venue is big or small!
ちゃんと見えてる 君のサイリウム
I can see it clearly, your penlight!
今はフーっと吹けば飛ぶような
Like something that would blow away with a puff,
小さな小さな才能だけど
it's a small, tiny talent, but—
私を推してくれるのなら
if you're going to support me,
アナタが味方でいてくれたら
as long as you are on my side,
爆レスをあげる
I'll give you explosive fanservice!
あなたのアイドル
Your idol,
サインはB♡ チュッ♡
The sign is B♡ (Chu♡)
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
Won't let a romantic scandal escape!
消してあげる
I'll wipe it out for you!
シル・ヴ・プレジデント
S'il vous président!
宣言！ 私が大統領になったら人の男にちょっかいかける女は島流しにします
Declaration! If I become president, any woman flirting with another woman's man will be exiled!
宣言！ 私が大統領になったらいやただの友達だよって誤魔化す奴はヘソから電気を流します
Declaration! Anyone playing dumb saying "we're just friends" will get shocked!
だ・だ・だ・大胆不敵
Daring and fearless!
センセーショナルクローズアップ
Sensational close-up!
D.D.D.Don't cry
D.D.D. Don't cry,
やるぜ徹底的にリサーチだ
we're gonna thoroughly research this!
大嫌い？ しょうがない？ クズは病気ね バイ・バイ・バイ
Hate it? Can't be helped? Scumbags are sick, bye-bye-bye!
権力！財産！地位名声！！なんにもないけど裁きたいでしょ？
Power, fortune, status and fame! You want to judge even with nothing?
1 2 3 だ・だ・だ・大統領になったらね
Once I become president,
まずは君を捕まえるね
first I'll capture you!
濡れたタオルで洗いざらい吐かせるね
With a wet towel, I'll make you spit out everything!
誰ですかあの女 ダメですかそうですか (あちゃ～)
Who is that woman? No good? Is that so? (Oops~)
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
Won't let a romantic scandal escape!
消してあげる
I'll wipe it out for you!
シル・ヴ・プレプレプレジデント
S'il vous... pré-pré-président!
宣言！ 私が大統領になったらただの仕事の付き合いだよって言う奴は二度と働けなくしてやります
Declaration! Anyone saying "it's just work" will never work again!
宣言！ 以下略！ いや向こうが強引でさーっていう男の口にはレジンを流し込んで固めてやります！
And for any guy saying "she forced herself," I'll pour resin in his mouth!
み・み・み・密着まるでドン・ファン気取りスキンダラス
Clinging tightly like a Don Juan pretender!
ま・ま・ま・末端価格 甲斐性なしのスクープね
Street value... what a spineless scoop!
愛はない？ 理由じゃない 悪くないのにはいはいはい
No love? That's not the reason! Even though it's fine, yeah, yeah, yeah!
軽薄！のうのう！いりしゃしゃー！！なんにもないとかありえないでしょ？
Frivolous, smug, shameless! It's impossible to have nothing, right?
1 2 3 だ・だ・だ・大統領になってもね
Even if I become president,
多分君は変わらないね
you probably won't change!
しらっとぼけて のらりくらりかわすのね (で・で・て！)
Playing dumb and dodging smoothly (De-de-te!)
デートですか こんばんは 本気ですか そうですか (ぽちゃ～)
Is this a date? Good evening. Are you serious? Is that so? (Pocha~)
情熱とは不注意 微熱も消してしまいたい
Passion is carelessness; I want to erase even a slight fever!
だ・だ・だ・だ 大統領になったらね
Da-da-da-da, if I become president,
マジで君を捕まえるね
I'll seriously capture you.
濡れたタオルで 洗いざらい吐かせるね
With a wet towel, I'll make you confess.
どこですか 今あんた
Where are you right now?
見っけちゃった バレちゃった
Found you, busted!
夜道には ご用心 さよなら
Watch your step on the night road, goodbye.
代わりに銃声
Instead, a gunshot.
シル・ヴ・プレ・プレ・プレジデント
S-s-s-sil vous president!
テンパってんパって焦ってんで
Tempted, flustered, and impatient,
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
あんた今夜も忘れたいこと 悲しいこと あるのかしら
Tonight too, is there something you want to forget or feel sad about?
知らない映画なのに涙を流すのは
Crying during an unknown movie
ドラマチックが足りないからよ
is because there's not enough drama.
そんなごみ箱かないこと くだらないこと あがってばかりね
Such trash cans, trivial things, always rising.
雨が上がれば愛も揃うよくが
If the rain clears up, love will align too,
誰かのものになるでしょ
it'll become someone's.
初発のパンチリーシャも全部 恋のためよ
The initial punch-leash is all for love.
じゃない一体どうしてどうして なんでなのと果てな不完全な家庭な
Why on earth, why, why to the end, an incomplete family,
冗談じゃないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
No kidding, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たってどうにもなんないし
Even if that time comes, nothing can be done,
曖昧なことなんて笑い飛ばすだけ
just laugh off ambiguous things.
あー 東京の貸しはハートばっかりよ 救いようもないわ
Ah, Tokyo's loans are all hearts, there's no saving them.
自堕落のない感情包丁いたって 夜な夜な誰のせいなのよ
Indolent emotion, wielding a knife night after night, whose fault is it?
私の勝手な傷もじっとこらえて 取り繕う予定はとうとう理解して
Enduring my own selfish wounds, finally understanding the pretense plans.
ねがろ年中リップサービス どうかんかましまし壁際キック
Year-round lip service, empathy boosted, wall kick.
頭の中のミュージックのせいで あなたの話は一向に聞き取れない
Because of the music in my head, I can't catch a word of your talk.
少しはまともなこと言って もう全部忘れさせてよ
Say something decent for once, let me forget everything.
だけど一体どうしてどうして なんでなのと果てな不完全な家庭な
Yet why on earth, why, why to the end, an incomplete family,
冗談じゃないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
No kidding, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たってどうにもなんないし
Even if that time comes, nothing can be done,
曖昧なことなんて笑い飛ばすだけ
just laugh off ambiguous things.
あたしをさっさとつないでいて神yes
Quickly connecting me, God yes.
冗談じゃないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
No kidding, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たってどうにもなんないし
Even if that time comes, nothing can be done.
不気味ないわ 感情なんて何度利口で落とすだけ
Eerie, emotions just dropped with how many times smart.
あたしと確かめ合っている街
The town where we confirm with each other.
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ その時が来たってどうにもなんないし
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous, even if that time comes nothing can be done.
曖昧なことなんて笑い飛ばすだけ あたしをさっさとつないでいて神yes
Just laugh off ambiguous things, quickly connecting me, God yes.
二酸化炭素をはきだして あの子が呼吸をしているよ
Exhaling carbon dioxide, that child is breathing.
どんてんもようの空の下 つぼみのままでゆれながら
Under a gloomy sky, swaying while still a bud.
野良犬はぼくの骨くわえ 野生の力をためしてる
A stray dog holds my bone, testing its wild power.
路地裏に月がおっこちて 犬の目玉は四角だよ
The moon fell into the back alley, a dog's eyeballs are square.
今日 人類がはじめて 木星に着いたよ
Today humanity reached Jupiter for the first time.
ピテカントロプスになる日も 近づいたんだよ
The day we become Pithecanthropus has also drawn near.
二酸化炭素をはきだして
Exhaling carbon dioxide,
あの子が呼吸をしているよ
that child is breathing.
街のはずれの夢のあと
In the dream aftermath at the edge of town,
つばさをつくしたペガサスが 夜空にハシゴをかけている
a wingless Pegasus hangs a ladder in the night sky.
武器をかついだ兵隊さん
Soldiers carrying weapons
南にいこうとしてるけど
are trying to head south, but
サーベルの音はチャラチャラと
the clinking sound of sabers
街の空気を汚してる
is polluting the air of the town.
今日人類がはじめて
Today, humankind for the very first time
木星に着いたよ
has reached Jupiter.
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
has also drawn closer.
歌を忘れたカナリア
A canary that forgot how to sing,
牛を忘れた牛小屋
a cowshed that forgot its cows—
こわれた磁石を ひろい 集める 博士はまるはげさ
the doctor picking up and gathering broken magnets is completely bald!
あの子は花火を打ち上げて この日が来たのを祝ってる
That child is shooting off fireworks, celebrating that this day has come.
冬の花火は強すぎて ぼらの身体はくだけ散る
Winter fireworks are too intense; our bodies shatter to pieces.
ブーゲンビリアの木の下で ぼくはあの子を探すけど
Under the bougainvillea tree, I search for that child,
月の光にじゃまされて あの子のかけらはみつからない
but obstructed by the moonlight, I can't find her fragments.
今日人類がはじめて 木星に着いたよ
Today, humankind for the very first time has reached Jupiter.
ピテカントロプスになる日も 近づいたんだよ
The day we become Pithecanthropus has also drawn closer.
さるにはなりたくない さるにはなりたくない
I don't want to become a monkey... I don't want to become a monkey...
こわれた磁石を 砂浜でひろっているだけさ
I'm just picking up broken magnets on the sandy beach.
あの日は花火を打ち上げて この日が来たのを祝ってる
That child is shooting off fireworks, celebrating that this day has come.
冬の花火は強すぎて ぼらの身体はくだけ散る
Winter fireworks are too intense; our bodies shatter to pieces.
ブーゲンビリアの木の下で ぼくはあの子を探すけど
Under the bougainvillea tree, I search for that child,
月の光にじゃまされて あの子のかけらはみつからない
but obstructed by the moonlight, I can't find her fragments.
今日人類がはじめて 木星に着いたよ
Today, humankind for the very first time has reached Jupiter.
ピテカントロプスになる日も 近づいたんだよ
The day we become Pithecanthropus has also drawn closer.
武器をかついだ兵隊さん 南にいこうとしてるけど
Soldiers carrying weapons are trying to head south, but
サーベルの音はチャラチャラと 街の空気を汚してる
the clinking sound of sabers is polluting the air of the town.
今日人類がはじめて 木星に着いたよ
Today, humankind for the very first time has reached Jupiter.
ピテカントロプスになる日も 近づいたんだよ
The day we become Pithecanthropus has also drawn closer.
歌を忘れたカナリア 牛を忘れた牛小屋
A canary that forgot how to sing, a cowshed that forgot its cows—
こわれた磁石を ひろい 集める 博士はまるはげさ
the doctor picking up and gathering broken magnets is completely bald!
あの日は花火を打ち上げて この日が来たのを祝ってる
That child is shooting off fireworks, celebrating that this day has come.
冬の花火は強すぎて ぼらの身体はくだけ散る
Winter fireworks are too intense; our bodies shatter to pieces.
ブーゲンビリアの木の下で ぼくはあの子を探すけど
Under the bougainvillea tree, I search for that child,
月の光にじゃまされて あの子のかけらはみつからない
but obstructed by the moonlight, I can't find her fragments.
さるにはなりたくない さるにはなりたくない
I don't want to become a monkey... I don't want to become a monkey...
こわれた磁石を 砂浜でひろっているだけさ
I'm just picking up broken magnets on the sandy beach.
今日人類がはじめて 木星に着いたよ
Today, humankind for the very first time has reached Jupiter.
ピテカントロプスになる日も 近づいたんだよ
The day we become Pithecanthropus has also drawn closer.
さるになるよ さるになるよ
I'll become a monkey... I'll become a monkey...
さるになるよ
I'll become a monkey...
朝まで踊る夢だけ見せて
Let me dream of dancing until dawn,
時計の鐘が解く魔法
the magic that the clock's bell breaks.
曖昧な指誘う階段
Vague fingers beckon me to the stairs,
三段飛ばしに跳ねていく
leaping up three steps at a time.
馬車の中で震えてた
Shivering inside the carriage,
みじめな古着めくりめぐれよ
turning over miserable old clothes.
夜の舞踏見知らぬ顔探す
Searching for unfamiliar faces at the night ball,
囁くあの声が握りしめた
that whispering voice clenched tightly.
刃突きだすすべてを奪えと
Pointing the blade: seize everything!
朝まで踊る夢だけ見せて
Show me only the dream of dancing until morning
時計の鐘が解く魔法
the magic unlocked by the clock's bell.
曖昧な指誘う階段
The vaguely beckoning stairs,
三段飛ばしに跳ねていく
bouncing up three steps at a time.
すべてを奪えと
To steal everything away...
孤児集う城
An orphanage-gathering castle,
笑み仮面に描いて
drawn on a smiling mask.
偽りの慈しみさえ
Even false affection...
羽で包む熾天使
A seraph wrapped in feathers.
灰の中で
In the ashes,
赤く溶けて混じる
melting and mixing in red.
硝子の靴
Glass shoes,
今更帰る
returning now, of all times.
震えているの
I'm trembling,
あなたが目をやる時計
the clock you're looking at.
靴脱ぎ踊るスロープ抜けて
Dancing off my shoes, slipping past the slope,
喉まで伸びる指の先で
with fingertips stretching to my throat.
すくう雫口付けて
Scooping droplets, kissing them,
走る衝動背骨抜けていく刹那
the impulse to run piercing through my spine.
鐘は鳴らさないで
Don't ring the bell,
あなたにひざまずき
kneeling down before you.
まだダメと叫んだ右手がい
My right hand screaming "not yet",
突き刺すサヨナラ
a piercing farewell.
消えない硝煙を香にまとう姫
A princess draped in the scent of gunpowder,
強い瞳僕の凍った仮面ごと打ち抜く
piercing right through my gaze and frozen mask.
今も耳にあなたの吐息が突き刺さるの遠い夢
Even now, your sigh pierces my ears in a distant dream.
ステンドグラス越し
Through the stained glass,
光る月が君にかぶせたベール
the shining moon placed a veil over you.
ドレス膝で裂いて
Tearing my dress at the knees,
ティアラは投げ捨てて
throwing away the tiara.
見つめ合う瞳と瞳が火花を放つ
Eyes gazing at eyes, sparking fire.
孤独な魂が炎あげ惹かれあう
Lonely souls ignite and are drawn to each other,
その涙すくえないならまるで一人遊び
if those tears can't be saved, it's like playing alone.
時よ止まれ今はあなたに酔いしれて
Stop time, now I'm intoxicated by you,
揺れる鼓動一つ一つを刻み付けたい
I want to etch every single beating pulse.
とどまれ熱く濡れ打ち付ける昂りに
Stay hot and wet against the pounding elation,
これ以上は動けないよまるで御伽噺
I can't move anymore, like a fairytale.
みんな、ここからは大事なお知らせタイムなのら！
Everyone, from here on is an important announcement time!
ぱぱ、ぱぱはそこで見ててななのらね！
Papa, Papa, watch from over there, nanorane!
では、まずは、こちらっ！
Now, first of all, here!
姫森ルーナ誕生日記念2025のグッズが出ますのら！
Himemori Luna's Birthday Commemoration 2025 goods are out!
ではね、こちら詳細見ていきましょう！
Now then, let's look at the details here!
ふたりのルーナ♡アクリルジオラマスタンドなのだ！イラストはトワル先生に描いていただきました！
The "Two Luna's Acrylic Diorama Stand"! The illustration was drawn by Doiru-sensei!
前のね、髪型と今回のルーナのね、新しい髪型のルーナが、そして今回の生誕ライブのステージに登場しました！
The previous hairstyle and Luna's new hairstyle appeared on this birthday live stage!
こちらはね、立体的なパーツが華やかで可愛い素敵な豪華仕様のジオラマスタンドになってます！
This diorama stand features gorgeous, cute 3D parts in a luxurious specification!
そして、次はこちら！姫森ルーナぬいぐるみ♡守ってルーナイトver.！
And next is this! Himemori Luna plushie ♡ Protect me Roonight ver.!
はい、届きました！
Yes, they have arrived!
姫森ルーナのぬいぐるみー
Himemori Luna's plushie—
守ってルーナイトver.のあなたがぬいぐるみに、なりましたー！
turned into a plushie in the Protect Your Knight ver., nano!
ぜひぜひみんなおうちににお迎えして、あなたをね、守ってほしいのなよ！
Please everyone, take one home and let it protect you, nano!
そして、次はこちら！
And next is this!
ルーナイト2wayバッグ！
The Lunaknight 2-way bag!
さっきのぬいぐるみもすっぽり入ってしまうルーナイトがアピールできるバッグなのだ！
A bag that can fit the plushie nicely and lets you show off your Lunaknight pride!
バッグはね、なんとリュックにもなって超便利！
And the bag even turns into a backpack—super convenient!
デザインに使用されているモチーフはルーナイト由来のもので統一しているので、バッグモードでもリュックモードでもお好きな方で使ってください！
The design uses unified Lunaknight motifs, so please use it as either a shoulder bag or backpack however you like!
次はこちら！
Next is this!
ルーナイトカードホルダー♡
The Lunaknight Card Holder ♡
ルーナイト型のカードホルダーです！
It's a Lunaknight-shaped card holder!
チェキ風カードやほろかのカードも入れられちゃうのでルーナイトのみんなはこっちもしかと守ってくださいね！
It can fit polaroid-style cards and Holoca cards too, so all you Lunaknights make sure to protect this as well, nano!
そして次はこちら！
And next is this!
ASMRボイス「舞踏会の帰り道」
ASMR Voice: "The Way Home from the Ball"
今回はね、舞踏会をイメージした生誕祭ライブなのでルーナイトとキロに着いたひとときをボイスにしました！
This time, since it's a birthday live themed around a ball, I made a voice drama about the moment arriving home with a Lunaknight!
馬車の中という密室でなんか急接近とかあちゃうかもー？
Being in a private carriage together... maybe we'll get a little too close for comfort?
ということで、最後に改めてフルセットを見てみましょう！
With that, let's take another look at the full set!
こちら、フルセット購入特典は…
Here are the full set purchase bonuses...
ででん！
Ta-da!
オリジナルカード！
Original Card!
イラストはゾイる先生で、表面がチェキ風のカードになってます！裏面は招待状風のデザインになっていておしゃれなのだ！
Illustrated by Zoi-ru-sensei, the front is a polaroid-style card! The back has an invitation-style design, which is so stylish, nano!
通常バージョンのフルセット購入特典は、箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカード！
The standard version full set bonus is a foil-stamped replica signed polaroid-style bromide card!
数量限定バージョンのフルセット購入特典は、直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードなのだ！
The quantity-limited version full set bonus is a hand-signed polaroid-style bromide card, nano!
みんなゲットしてほしいのな！
I hope everyone gets it, nano!
なんっしょいぱっしょん
Nansshoi Passhon!
こちらのね、この後歌わせていただきます。
We'll be singing this song right after this.
みんなね大好きな「なんっしょい」っていう言葉を使っているのなのでみんなこの後いっぱいなんっしょいしてね！
It uses everyone's favorite word "nansshoi," so everyone make sure to shout "nansshoi" lots after this, nano!
この配信が終わったらMVも公開されます！
Once this stream ends, the MV will also be released!
そして、MV公開の日めげが今回初めてやる事になったのでこちらもお楽しみに！
And since this is the first time doing a premiere for an MV release, please look forward to that too, nano!
ではね、歌います！
Well then, let's sing!
なんっしょいぱっしょん！
Nansshoi Passhon!
なんなんなん泣きたい
Na-na-na-na, I want to cry,
別に起きとこかねのら！
staying up late anyway, nano!
なんっしょいぱっしょん
Nansshoi Passhon!
むにゃいむにゃい目をこする
Rubbing my sleepy, sleepy eyes,
囚われた城にパーフェクトめな朝
a prisoner in a castle with a picture-perfect morning.
おないおないお布団から飛び出して海へ行こう
Jumping right out of my futon, let's head out to the sea!
神様だって間違いんだって
Even gods can make mistakes,
よくある話だそうです
or so the story goes.
姫様にね見とれちゃうんだって
Falling under the spell of Her Highness,
やれやれなのだらね
good grief, nano!
夢を夢見て
Dreaming within a dream,
恋に恋して生きていたい！だから
living and falling in love! That's why
これでいいのだら！
this is just fine, nano!
なんなんなん泣きたい笑いたい
Na-na-na-na, crying and laughing,
心だって自ら手を変えるのだら
we change our hearts with our own hands, nano!
だから逢いたいその願いにいま約束の合言葉
That's why I want to see you—the password of our promise now,
行くよ！なんっしょい！
here we go! Nansshoi!
まどろみもホラーな夜もあるけど でもね！なんっしょい！
There are drowsy nights and spooky nights too, but you know what? Nansshoi!
いつまでもみんなおりゅから平気
Everyone will always be here, so it's okay,
まだ遊び足りねえのだら！
we haven't played enough yet, nano!
暗い 暗い 夜 の 中
In the dark, dark night,
ティアラ を 外し て
taking off my tiara
城 を 抜け たら
and sneaking out of the castle,
深い 深い 海 に 出 て
going out to the deep, deep sea...
…バレてん の らく と ないー
...getting caught would be no fun—!
姫 様 は ね わがまま なんて
A princess being selfish—
おとぎ の 話 よ そうでしょう？
that's just a fairytale, right?
何 が なん だって 私 なん だって
No matter what, no matter who I am,
これ で いい のら ！！
this is fine just as it is!
ん ・ な ・ な ・ なりたい
I want to be
私 で いたい ！
just who I am!
どこ へ だって 向かって ゆける のら ！
I can head anywhere I want!
ならば しょうがない この 想い に
So it can't be helped, to these feelings
今 許さ れる 合言葉
now the passcode is granted—
いく よっ ！ なん しょうい ！！
Here we go! Nanshois!!
サンゴ礁 白い 砂浜 も 綺麗 そこ に
Coral reefs and white sandy beaches are lovely, right there—
なん しょうい ！！
Nanshois!!
輝く 私
Shining as myself,
Q . 帰る 理由 は ？
Q: The reason for returning?
A . そこ に なけれ ば ね のら ！
A: Because if it's not there, no way!
なぁぁぁい ！
Noooo way!
りぴーとあふみー
Repeat after me!
なんしょうい！！ なんしょうい！！ せーのっ！ なんしょうい！！
Nanshois!! Nanshois!! Ready, set! Nanshois!!
もう1回！ なんしょうい！！ なんしょうい！！
Once more! Nanshois!! Nanshois!!
熱い 視線 が 集中
Heated gazes are focused on me,
ハラハラ する 心 に 無我夢中 だから
my heart flutters, I'm completely entranced, so—
だ から
so—
これ で いい のら ！！
this is fine just as it is!
ん ・ な ・ な ・ 泣きたい から 笑い たい
N-n-n-want to cry, so I want to laugh!
こころ だって 奪って あげる のら ！
I'll steal your heart away too!
だから 「 会い たい 」 その 願い に
So to that wish of "I want to see you,"
今 約束 の 合言葉
now the promised passcode—
いく よっ ！ なん しょうい ！！
Here we go! Nanshois!!
まどろみ も ホラー な 夜 も ある けど でも ね
There are drowsy nights and horror nights too, but you know—
なん しょうい ！！
Nanshois!!
この 先 も みんな おりゅ から へいき まだ 遊び 足りねえ のら ！
From here on out everyone is here, so we're fine, we haven't played enough yet!
まだ 遊び 足りねえ のら ！
We haven't played enough yet!
生誕ライブに来てくれてありがとぅ～！！今年は体調不良の時期だったから声が出なかったかもしれない…TOT
Thank you so much for coming to my birthday live!! This year I had a rough patch with my health, so maybe my voice didn't come out right... TOT
でも最後まで頑張ったのだ！！うりゃぁい！！
But I did my best until the very end!! Uryaai!!
これからもずっと姫様に愛を忠誠をを ❤️ I Love You ちゃばちゃば 💋 (♡・o・♡)
From now on too, give your love and loyalty forever to the Princess ❤️ I Love You chabachaba 💋 (♡・o・♡)
2025.10.10 るーなのらっ☆
2025.10.10 Luna-nora☆